# Pratima Budahthoki Junior Flutter Developer

□ pratmabdth7@gmail.com

9861444977

Kathmandu

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/pratima-budhathoki-3a7493248/

## **PROFILE**

Am a Mobile Developer who has around 1 years of experience with Flutter Hybrid Mobile App development. If looking for a highly skilled and rich experienced mobile expert with a deep knowledge, a professional attitude, excellent communication skills and the highest code quality, then I'm the person looking for. Over this year I've built many apps of several fields for Android and Flutter apps. Principles As a freelancer, take great pride in making sure all of projects are up to client's satisfaction, all deadlines are met and quality assurance is carefully considered.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2022 – 2023 Onviro Tech P.Ltd, Junior Flutter Developer

Kathmadnu, Nepal Tech company, offer a comprehensive suite of services designed to

leverage the power of technology expertise spans across software development, mobile app development, web design and development, cloud computing solutions, data analytics, artificial intelligence, and

machine learning.

2019 – 2021 **3DMS Trader,** Manager

Kathmandu, Nepal It is an interior decoration Company working on their own product as

requirement of client preference and styles.it include from selection themes, design, scheme, flooring materials, furniture artwork along with

different accessories.

## **EDUCATION**

2019 – 2023 Ambition College, Bachelor in Computer Application

Kathmandu, Nepal

Bijeshwori Gyan Mandir Sainik Mahavidyalaya, +2 NEB

Kathmadnu, Nepal

2016 - 2018

### **LANGUAGES**

English | Nepali | Hindi

# **SKILLS**

Dart Programming language • Flutter • Html/CSS • Java Script • UI/UX

Mobile App Development SDK • php • Git • Mobile Programming

# **INTERESTS**

Reading • Hiking • Photography • Fitness • Coding • Research

#### **PROJECTS**

## App Development, Dailomaa App

Dailomaa is Ecommerce app , Nepal first online stationary store provide all the consumer electronics

As a juniors flutter developer at Onviro tech I played a pivotal role in the development and management of an innovative eCommerce application, contributing to its success and growth. My responsibilities and achievements included Application development, User Experience (UX),Inventory Management, Mobile Responsiveness Integration, Data Analytics, error handling

# App Development, Dailomaa Delivery App

During my tenure as a Júnior Flutter developer at Onviro tech , I played a pivotal role in the development and management of an advanced delivery app, which significantly contributed to streamlining delivery operations and enhancing customer experiences. My key role is to maintain the App, Designing the user interface, Fetching the Data from APi ,Notification System

# App Development, Chatify

Chatify is the social media app where user can chat, post and add a story to their account . user can even follow and unfollow each other on this platform .I played a pivotal role in the development and management of a dynamic social media app, contributing to its growth . My responsibilities and accomplishments included App Development, Algorithmic Feed, Integration, State Management, UI/UX development.

## Website, Doctor Appointment system

The Doctor Appointment System is the website which Facilities user to take appointment of the doctor through online . user can select the doctors according to their qualification , education and budget. The project contains an admin and user sides. the admit side manage the management like doctor records , patients records, appointment time treatment facilities and so on.

## App Development, Ditya\_ms

The Ditya\_MS App is a user-friendly mobile application designed to streamline and simplify the process of applying for overseas job opportunities. With this app, job seekers can easily complete their applications, submit their qualifications, and efficiently connect with potential employers in foreign countries. Seeking a position as a App Developer to leverage my expertise in designing, developing, and optimizing applications that streamline workforce operations, enhance productivity, and improve resource allocation like Mobile App Development, User-Friendly Interfaces, Real-Time Communication, Data Analytics, UI/UX, Fetching API